MUHAMMAD SADAM MAHENDRA

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

085156321345 | sadam.mahendra@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/m-sadam-m | https://github.com/SadamMahendra

Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Fresh graduate of Information Technology from Darma Persada University. Experience of participating in the Independent Study "Kampus Merdeka" on Front-End Web Developer and React, makes me have interpersonal and communication skills, as well as good knowledge related to software development. I am a passionate and hardworking person, always working effectively with attention to detail, and also have a high motivation to succeed and always enthusiastic in learning new things.

Work Experience

PT. Presentologics - Bandung, Jawa Barat

Aug, 2022 - Dec, 2022

Front-End and React Web Developer independent study

- Modified software applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript based on specifications.
- Managed code in a Github repository and collaborated with other developers.
- Developed React web apps that utilize functional components, stateful components, and controlled components well. Apply property
 validation, routing, component lifecycle, context, and hooks well.
- Designed a final capstone project, in terms of application/solution development. Won the award for the best team in the Capstone Project.

Project Experiences

Smile App Web - Dicoding Project

Aug, 2022 - Dec, 2022

Front-End and React Web Developer

- Developing a parent website as a smile app using HTML, CSS, Javascript and react is with the team.
- Creating a smile app website for the final capstone project.

Library Web - Intern Project

Mar, 2022 - Jul, 2022

Full-Stack Developer

Contribute to creating a web library at SMPN 52 Bekasi City using the php programming language.

Education Level

Darma Persada University - Jakarta, Indonesia

2019 - 2023

Bachelor Degree of Informatics Engineering, 3.67/4.00

- Thesis Sentiment Analysis of Customer Satisfaction Levels Towards J&T Express Courier Services Using Support Vector Machine (SVM) Algorithm Based on User Reviews on Google PlayStore.
- Relevant Course Works: Database, Web Development and Python.

Courses, Training and Certifications

Dicoding Indonesia - Bandung, Jawa Barat

Aug, 2023 - Dec, 2022

Front-End and React Web Developer

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for parenting as a smile app, within five months.
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React Js.
- Certificate:
 - https://bit.ly/Sertifikat-Kelulusan
 - https://bit.ly/Sertifikat-Best-Caption

Skills

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Node.js, React Js, Python, PHP, GitHub.

Soft skills: Problem Solving, Time Management, Analytical Thinking and Teamwork

Languages: Indonesian (Native), English (Beginner)